[{
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “thing”?",
        "answer": "것",
        "choices": [
            "집 ",
            "침대",
            "것",
            "시간"
        ]
    }, {
        "question": "Fill in the blanks.지효는 물_ 마시다.",
        "answer": "을",
        "choices": [
            "를",
            "은",
            "을",
            "는"
        ]
    },

    {
        "question": "Fill in the blanks.나연_ 괴여워요!",
        "answer": "는",
        "choices": [
            "를",
            "가",
            "언니",
            "는"
        ]
    },

    {
        "question": "Translate this sentence. She walks to school",
        "answer": "그녀는 학교에 걷는다",
        "choices": [
            "그녀가 교실에 간다",
            "그녀는 학교에 걷는다",
            "그는 은행에 사다",
            "그는 고기를 먹고싶어"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Translate this sentence. 미나는 똑똑해요.",
        "answer": "Mina is smart.",
        "choices": [
            "Mina is chubby.",
            "Mina is smart.",
            "Mina is cute.",
            "Mina is beautiful."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Translate this sentence. 나연는 어젯밤에 소주를 마셨어.",
        "answer": "Nayeon drank soju last night.",
        "choices": [
            "Nayeon ate supper last night.",
            "Nayeon prayed to god last night.",
            "Nayeon drank soju last night.",
            "Nayeon told Tzuyu a bedtime story last night."
        ]
    }, {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a valid Korean sentence structure?",
        "answer": "Subject-Noun (SN)",
        "choices": [
            "Subject-Adjective (SA)",
            "Subject-Object-Verb (SOV)",
            "Subject-Verb (SV)",
            "Subject-Noun (SN)"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following are pronouns?",
        "answer": "나",
        "choices": [
            "나",
            "사",
            "시",
            "십"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the english translation of  행복하다?",
        "answer": "happy",
        "choices": [
            "sad",
            "smart",
            "handsome",
            "happy"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct sequence of time in chronological order?",
        "answer": "아침, 점심, 저녁",
        "choices": [
            "점심, 저녁, 아침",
            "아침, 점심, 저녁",
            "저녁, 아침, 점심 ",
            "아침,, 저녁,점심"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "This word particle is used if the last letter of the subject is a consonant",
        "answer": "는",
        "choices": [
            "를",
            "은",
            "을",
            "는"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “eat food”?",
        "answer": "음식을 먹다",
        "choices": [
            "먹다 음식",
            "먹다 사과",
            "길물",
            "음식을 먹다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What particle is to be use in “여자__”",
        "answer": "는",
        "choices": [
            "는",
            "나",
            "은",
            "을"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “sad”?",
        "answer": "슬프다",
        "choices": [
            "아름답다",
            "통통하다",
            "슬프다",
            "행복하다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following corresponds to “house, bed, window”?",
        "answer": "집, 침대, 창문",
        "choices": [
            "집, 침대, 창문",
            "창문, 사과, 침대",
            "것, 침대, 창문",
            "사다, 써다, 읽다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “time”",
        "answer": "시간",
        "choices": [
            "아침",
            "점심",
            "저녁",
            "시간"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “hate”?",
        "answer": "싫어하다",
        "choices": [
            "싫어하다",
            "아름답다 ",
            "좋아하다",
            "마시다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the english translation of “통통하다 ”?",
        "answer": "plump",
        "choices": [
            "happy",
            "sad",
            "plump",
            "tasty"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the english translation of “바나나”?",
        "answer": "banana",
        "choices": [
            "plump",
            "banana",
            "happy",
            "handsome"
        ]
    }

]